A Finding Aid to the Emilio Sanchez Papers, 1922-2012, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Unprocessed Addition to the Emilio Sanchez Papers, 1949-2012; Series 7; Archival Resource Key; 10.1 Linear feet boxes 25-34, OV 35
  - Unprocessed Papers, 1949-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 26)
  - Unprocessed Papers, 1949-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 27)
  - Unprocessed Papers, 1949-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 28)
  - Unprocessed Papers, 1949-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 29)
  - Unprocessed Papers, 1949-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 30)
  - Unprocessed Papers, 1949-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 31)
  - Unprocessed Papers, 1949-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 32)
  - Unprocessed Papers, 1949-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 33)
  - Unprocessed Papers, 1949-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 34)
  - Unprocessed Oversize Material, 1949-2012; Archival Resource Key (Oversize 35)